[Music]
I want to show everybody um that you can
be your most authentic self at work
because I am here I made it and I'm not
hiding my true identity I I want my
story to inspire others so that they can
be themselves that they not hiding
they're not feeling like their sexual
orientation or gender
is a hinder to their de Career
Development or their progress at work
when I share my personal
story it wasn't my intention to pressure
anybody to come out they will decide
where when and how at the most
convenient time um and when they feel
most comfortable we Embrace
diversity and all form of differences
when you look at someone look at their
potential look at the quality of what
they contribute in the conversation in
the work that they do every day my name
is Janam and this is me
[Music]